hello YouTube welcome to my brand new
what is it called channel hello YouTube
but welcome to my brand new channel I'm
gonna show you exactly how I mastered 4x
in under 6 months with these 6 quick
tips using nothing more than my brain a
journal and some free education that I
found on YouTube just like this video so
in order to become as woke as me you're
gonna need to hit that like button let's
start with my background I come from an
IT background so I was easily able to
get into the Bitcoin rage before the
whole media caught on to it I was one of
the first people to get on that
bandwagon in 2017 when the market cycle
had just started a type safe to say it
was a really fun time we made a lot of
money and everyone was really excited
until we lost it all luckily enough I
was able to cash up some of my profits
along the way learning lots of lessons
basics of reading charts and terrible
retail trading strategies it
successfully learned how to buy high and
sell for a loss or to FOMO into a trade
and lose half of my account within the
next thirty minutes or even accidentally
click the wrong button and get
liquidated instantly good times jokes
aside this was the first lesson in my
journey how to feel pain and this is
gonna be the first lesson that you're
gonna have to experience to is
appreciate the pain of losing without
suffering there cannot be success and in
the same way that you cannot feel cold
without warm there needs to be the
balance between the two what I'm saying
is failure is crucial in order for
success to be born you're not going to
just have six
without failing along the way and
learning to grow so you're really gonna
have to appreciate those failures and
know that from the failure you will grow
and you will get better and I already
know what you're saying to yourself
you're saying Connor I would much rather
not feel the pain of failure and just
win all the time well of course you
would cupcake but this ain't the world
we live in is much better to lose early
on and grow from those losses than to
just continue to succeed until you have
that 100k account until you've never
really learned how to successfully trade
and manage your money and then make that
major mistake and lose a hundred grand
instead of five hundred dollars that
you're starting with now this is gonna
take some times to surpass this pain
period and you're gonna have to endure
the pain and then eventually you'll reap
the rewards that's tip number one endure
the pain and suffering and learn to
appreciate it and you're gonna have to
make sure that that doesn't make you
give up fast forward to January 2019 I
started getting interested in forex
everything in the crypto space kind of
started getting boring
friends started dropping off they
weren't really around anymore so I
needed something else to start to learn
while crypto clearly wasn't the place
for my dreams to come true and I know
what you're gonna say you're gonna say
hunter you really started trading more
than six months ago because you had the
crypto advantage
isn't that clickbait yes but to be fair
I really didn't start trading Forex um
and it only took me about six months to
master forex the crypto thing was more
of an investment and a degenerate
gambling platform for me I wasn't really
serious about learning how to trade and
until until January of 2019 and then
from there it took me about six months
until I was able to become a
consistently profitable trader
anyways one of the biggest reasons I was
able to go from such losses losing
basically everything within a few weeks
to making consistently 10% a month was
my determination and the effort that I
was able to put in you see coming from
the IT background I had a lot of free
time sitting in front of a computer
whereas most other people working there
9 to 5 jobs they actually have to work
luckily IT guys we don't really have to
work that hard at least my jobs so
please don't go crying to your
girlfriend your mom your dad your
brother sister whatever and say how I
had an advantage and I was able to work
well I was able to study while at work
and if you really want something you're
gonna find a way to do it sitting in
front of a computer all day allowed me
to watch lots of YouTube videos while
smashing that like button and monitor my
trades more effectively live I was
basically able to learn at twice the
rate as a normal trader is able to learn
and so six months for me might be a year
for you I probably put in well over a
hundred thousand hours over those six
months that equates to roughly 60 hours
a week of studying and practice of my
trading so this brings us to our next
tip work your butt off this is gonna
take a long time and you're gonna need
to consistently be learning and putting
in as much effort as you can because you
never really know when you're gonna kind
of come across something that's gonna be
revolutionary for you kind of a
breakthrough or something that's really
crucial that's gonna help your trading
even years down the line moving forward
I had met a lot of friends from a crypto
community that a lot of them dropped off
really great guys but they don't really
trade the crypto anymore since things
got boring and only a very small few of
them actually came and joined me with
the Forex world and even after then they
started to dwindle down this left me
with only maybe three or four guys that
I was able to keep friendships with and
we were
really able to pass ideas along with
each other and and bounce ideas off of
each other and come up with different
strategies and if it wasn't for these
three or four people that I can
specifically think of by name then I
wouldn't be in the same place I am today
this is gonna be my next point you're
gonna have to find a community or a
group of friends or something that's
really gonna inspire each other you need
to have like-minded goals you need to
all be after the same final Prize or
final goal these guys are gonna be able
to give you ideas you're gonna be able
to give them ideas which will give them
other ideas that they can give to you
and then you can give back ideas and
you'll just keep getting ideas until you
don't know what to do with these ideas
anymore the catch here though is you
don't know who is gonna be able to give
you good ideas you don't know if they're
even gonna want to help you back or
they're just gonna take things from you
so you're really just gonna have to cast
your net far and wide and see who's able
there to help you after you help them
and you're really gonna need to offer
something for them in order for them to
want to give back to you so you're gonna
have to create that replica City so
that's tip number three find a community
and if you don't know where to start
I've linked the in the description down
below just a discord community that
we're gonna start to gather a few people
and you guys can really just toss some
ideas around and the whole goal of the
community is just so that we can talk
and share ideas whether you use that
community and or you find your own
community your own friends that you can
find ideas off of and you found this
golden idea that you really thinks gonna
work and you're gonna be rich you can't
wait to tell your friends and your
family about this great idea and how
it's gonna work wonders hold on hold on
hold on not quite yet there's still a
couple things that we need to do before
we can get rich oh man hey you're gonna
no not want to lose the money right away
in just in case it's not a winning
strategy and B of course you're gonna
have to prove that it's a winning
strategy first and there's a faster way
we can do that
doing it live what you're gonna do is
you're gonna have to back test the
strategy that you think's gonna work you
can use something like trading view or
some other program I'm not sure of any
others I know trading view has a great
one that I will make a video on at some
point if you guys really want to see
that I don't know if people are really
interested in something like that or if
they already know how to do it so the
point of back-testing is twofold
you're gonna be able to test a lot more
data points a lot faster rather than
waiting for the live trades to come
along and then you take them and also
you're probably not on a winning
strategy most of the strategies are
going to lose so you're not gonna want
to keep throwing your real money
these strategies that you think are
gonna work just because somebody told
you or and you trust them you should
really got a backtest
everything that you come across if you
think it's gonna work for yourself don't
trust just anybody that gives you
information on YouTube that's tip number
four test your trading strategies from
wherever they come from
before you start dumping real money into
it and that's gonna be really quick
it'll only take you a few hours to get
maybe 50 data points or something if you
really do this optimally and I'll show
you a proper way to do it so that it's
most similar to what you would what you
would be doing lie I did say that there
was gonna be two things that you have to
do before you can start making it rich
and the second thing is to log your
trades so after you found a proven
strategy that's proven by the backtest
which we still don't know for sure if
it's going to work and then we can start
forward testing and it's very important
that you're gonna be logging your traits
and there's a reason why every
profitable trader including myself is
logging their trades and that reason is
that the markets change and you're gonna
narrow down that strategy into even
finer details to see what works even
better and better and if the market does
change and the strategy doesn't work in
where you're gonna figure out very
quickly that it's not working anymore
and you need to alter it to something
different right really all you're gonna
have to add into your log book and I can
give you guys an example of one later on
is you're you're mostly just gonna have
to add things like what pair you took
which actually isn't even that important
and but you're just gonna have to take
the profit or the losses write that down
and you're gonna have to write down what
parameters were present for you to take
the trade or what you saw in order to
take the trade and then that way we can
get an average over a long period of
time and you can do some maths using
magic of Excel and then you're gonna be
able to determine if it's a profitable
strategy even by live testing before I
give away my final tip if you like this
video which you did hit that like button
down below and I have a ton more ideas
for videos including my own personal
trading strategy so if you want to be a
manly man trader and get woke like me
then hit that subscribe button and the
Bell notification so you make sure to
never miss a video and don't forget
studies have shown that the harder you
hit the like button the more money you
make in the forex market okay so
everything sounds pretty easy right you
just have to follow the rules that can't
be too hard shouldn't be too hard
well you're right until you stop
following the rules and you start doing
something I like to call strategy slip
strategy slip is a term I'm gonna coin
right now it's basically when you've got
a proven system that you know is gonna
work in the long run but because the
markets either being boring or you're
eager or you're just feeling lucky
you're kind of breaking the rules just a
little bit just to squeeze in an extra
trade for that excitement factor and and
you're really not gonna be able to get
very good results if you just keep
slipping like this let me make this very
clear if you find a proven strategy
you've tested it you know it works and
you don't follow it strictly your dingus
this step may seem quite easy but
following your own rules and practicing
your self-discipline it's probably gonna
take you just as long as finding the
proven method you must practice and
become Zen with the market and never
enter a trade when you're bored
so that was our sixth tip practice
patience and discipline there you have
it the six tips that I took in the six
first months of trading forex that
allowed me to become the goat at trading
Forex in those six months I went from
losing all my money to becoming
consistently profitable and then the
following six months I was able to
nearly double my account